<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Labor Wage Statistics</string>
    <string name="select_occupation">Select Occupation</string>
    <string name="occupation_summary">Occupation Details</string>
    <string name="select_location">Select Location</string>
    <string name="top_industries">Top Industries</string>
    <string name="select_industry">Select Industry</string>
    <string name="top_occupations">Top Occupations</string>
    <string name="compare_salary">Compare Salary</string>
    <string name="top_locations">Top Locations</string>
    <string name="top_salary">Top Salary</string>
    <string name="top_employment">Top Employment</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="documentation">Documentation</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="no_data">No data available</string>
    <string name="occupation_selection_tooltip">Select your occupation.  You can filter the list by selecting an occupation group or pressing the Search button.</string>
    <string name="occupation_map_tooltip">Tap on a state marker to select a state and see its mean annual salary</string>
    <string name="occupation_map_state_tooltip">Tap on the state balloon to see the mean annual salaries for state cities</string>
    <string name="industry_selection_tooltip">Select your preferred industry.  You can filter the list by typing into the Search bar.</string>
    <string name="industry_occupation_selection_tooltip">Press the Back button to return to the list of occupations</string>
    <string name="location_map_tooltip">Tap on a state marker to select a state</string>
    <string name="location_map_state_tooltip">Tap on the \"View ... top occupations\" button at the top of the screen to select the state or city or tap on the state balloon to see the cities available within the state</string>
    <string name="compare_tooltip">Enter a yearly salary in the field at the top of the screen to see how your salary compares</string>
    <string name="compare_map_tooltip">Tap on a state marker to select a state</string>
    <string name="compare_state_map_select_state_tooltip">Tap on the \"Select ... \" button at the top of the screen to select the state</string>
    <string name="compare_city_map_select_state_tooltip">Tap on the state balloon to see the cities available within the state</string>
    <string name="compare_city_map_select_city_tooltip">Tap on the \"Select ... \" button at the top of the screen to select the city</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">THE MATERIAL EMBODIED IN THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED TO YOU "AS-IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE UNITED STATES DEPARTMENT OF LABOR (DOL) OR THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF PROFIT, LOSS OF USE, SAVINGS OR REVENUE, OR THE CLAIMS OF THIRD PARTIES, WHETHER OR NOT DOL OR THE U.S. GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS, HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE POSSESSION, USE, OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="api_disclaimer">This product uses the DOL Data API but is not endorsed or certified by the DOL</string>
</resources>
